

ALEN GUSINAC

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+46 793-260425

alengusinac.dev@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/alengusinac

github.com/alengusinac

Gothenburg, Sweden

TECH LANGUAGES











JavaScript TypeScript









MongoDb











Vue

EDUCATION **Frontend Developer**

Medieinstitutet

2022 - (2024)

Divemaster

Ouo Vadis Dive Resort

2018

Electrician (High School)

Viskastrandsgymnasiet

2010 - 2013

Emergency First Response Bartenderschool

HUMAN LANGUAGES

Swedish English German Bosnian

PROFILE

I am a happy and energetic 29 year old that studies his last year at Medieinstitutet to become a future promising frontend developer. Already as a young teen I spent time playing computer games and even had my own game-server for Tibia when I was 15 years old which I learned to build only by searching the web. I always want to progress and learn new things so after spending 8 years as an electrician, amongst other things, I was ready to take on the next big challenge to be part of the promising tech industry. My frontend course mainly focuses on JavaScript, with a few frameworks, together with HTML & CSS, UX/Usability, API-development, testing and design. If you're interested for more I would like to refer you to my personal letter, GitHub or LinkedIn. You're also welcome to contact me by email and telephone.

WORK EXPERIENCE

10+ years

Electrician

Tobias Söderens AB 2022 - 2023

Service electrician:

- Customer contact, job from start to finish, teaching interns.
- Focused on smaller private clients and some bigger jobs.

Ecokraft AB

Solar electrician:

- · Customer contact, job from start to finish, teaching interns.
- Mainly solar inverter installations on private villas and bigger solar fields.

Elkontakt AB 2013 - 2020

All-in-all electrician:

- Customer contact, job from start to finish, teaching interns.
- · Private smaller jobs planned together with customers.
- Month long projects away from home building big warehouses and apartment complexes.

Underwater Photographer & Divemaster

Quo Vadis Dive Resort 2018

- · Customer contact, scheduling, safety planning.
- Full responsibility of divers safety.
- · Selling photos to customers.

Bartender, Server & Cashier (Season)

Societen 2 summer seasons Björnvallens Sportkök 1 winter season Hotell Kittelfjäll 1 winter season

TECH PROJECTS







Live Site Code



Live Site Code



Code



ALEN GUSINAC

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN,

I'm studying my last year on the frontend developer program at Medieinstitutet and am hereby applying for the position of Junior Developer as full-time employed or as a freelance for some extra work as I already have my own company.

Courses that I have completed are HTML & CSS, JavaScript basics & advanced, Graphical tools, API-development, UX/Usability, Testing, Work methods and Agile project. I'm mostly passionate about JavaScript/TypeScript and see myself in a position where I can progress my skills in that area. Also working in a team in this line of work is something I'm really looking forward to.

With me in your team you can be certain to get a passionate and social person who likes to contribute to make everybody feel part of a project so both colleagues and customers are happy with the end result. I'm very welcoming and have no trouble with getting to know new people. Creating a good vibe to my surrounding happens naturally as I'm very conscious that everybody comes from different backgrounds and have different experiences both in work and in life.

I'm a jack of all trades and my journey with programming started when I moved into my self built van and took off for Portugal to progress my surfing and was missing something to do between surfs. As I get restless, the search for something to fill in the gaps began. I turned to google to check for possibilities to study programming and quickly got hooked for frontend developing. I did some free online courses at FreeCodeCamp, Codecademy and started following The Odin Project. Later I decided to get some more structured learning in and applied to Medieinstitutet which I got accepted for and have so far only had the highest grade.

One of my stronger sides is that I'm a quick learner thanks to my job as an electrician that has made me imply logical thinking and planing to faster be able to choose which road to take to reach my goals. If I feel that I'm repeating myself with a task, I prefer to spend some extra time to come up with a solution that can be reused to be able to spend less time and money in the future.

Very much looking forward hearing from you and in the future be able to progress with you.

ALEN GUSINAC

+46 793-260425

alengusinac.dev@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/alengusinac

ָר בָּ

github.com/alengusinac